{
    "subject": "resource/Paul_Lawrie",
    "predicate": "ontology/height",
    "object": "1.8034",
    "human_readable": "Paul Lawrie's height is 1.8034 meters.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8910574316978455,
            "question": "Is Paul Lawrie considered tall?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8853945732116699,
            "question": "What is Paul Lawrie's height?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7934390306472778,
            "question": "Express Paul Lawrie's height in feet and inches."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7566571831703186,
            "question": "What unit of measurement is used for Paul Lawrie's height?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7337075471878052,
            "question": "What other physical characteristics might be associated with someone who is 1.8034 meters tall?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7010848522186279,
            "question": "How many centimeters is Paul Lawrie's height?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6725672483444214,
            "question": "Imagine Paul Lawrie standing next to someone who is 1.70 meters tall. Who is taller?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6439325213432312,
            "question": "Could you compare Paul Lawrie's height to the average male height?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5995684862136841,
            "question": "Is there any significance to the decimal places in Paul Lawrie's height?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5831816792488098,
            "question": "Could you provide an example of a situation where knowing Paul Lawrie's height would be helpful?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Paul Lawrie's height is 1.8034 meters.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2211_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any significance to the decimal places in Paul Lawrie's height?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2211_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could you compare Paul Lawrie's height to the average male height?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2211_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Imagine Paul Lawrie standing next to someone who is 1.70 meters tall. Who is taller?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2211_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2211_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2211_119.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2211_125.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2211_128.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2211_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2211_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2211_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2211_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2211_92.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2211_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text states that Paul Lawrie's height was around 5 feet 11 inches.  There's no mention of his height in meters. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context information provides that Paul Lawrie\u2019s height was around 5 feet 11 inches, which is approximately 1.8034 meters. However, the provided statement uses a more precise measurement than what is given in the documents, so it would be considered incorrect based on the available information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}